jobslab.in 2018-06-15

# Privacy Policy - JobsLab

The privacy of our visitors is important to us.

JobsLab.in has created this privacy statement to describe our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: “JobsLab.in” at http://www.jobslab.in. We seek to protect your private information so that you have a pleasurable viewing experience on our Web site. We will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. Please return to this page from time to time, as we will be updating this statement as our services continue to grow. We welcome and encourage questions, comments, and suggestions. Please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with any questions.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies store information about your use of a particular Web site or service and are typically used to make services more convenient and personalized. Most cookies are “session cookies,” which are automatically deleted whenever you leave a Web site, although some cookies remain on your computer until you remove them.

 **Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser(s) (i.e. Google, Tribal Fusion, Advertising.com, DoubleClick and/or others) may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

 **How We Use Cookies**  
We use cookies  
(1) to estimate the number of visitors to our Web site  
(2) to measure general traffic patterns, and  
(3) to personalize information and services we provide to you on the site.

Companies that place ads on the JobsLab.in Web site — including, but not limited to Tribal Fusion, AOL Advertising.com, LiJit, BurstMedia (Blinx), Google, Infolinks, DoubleClick and/or others — may also use their own cookies to help determine the frequency and placement of particular ads. Your browser controls how cookies are used and can be set to not allow them. However, it is possible that some parts of the JobsLab.in site may not function properly if your browser refuses our cookies. We may, from time to time, use cookies to store your zip code and email address for use with certain current or future services such as e-mail update list(s), showtimes e-mail services, local showtimes profiles, theater and movie preference profiles.

 **Cookie Notification and Disabling**  
Most browsers permit you to set the browser to accept, reject, or notify you of cookie use. However, some parts of the JobsLab.in Web site may not function properly if your browser is set to reject cookies.

 **Demographic Information**  
Demographic information may be collected on the web site. The information will only be shared with any third-parties in an aggregate format.

 **Log Files**  
JobsLab.in, both using its own systems and the systems of others (such as Google or Quantcast, among others) automatically logs information such as IP addresses, ISPs, and browser type but does not link that information to personally identifying information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

 **Sharing of Information**  
JobsLab.in is engaged in “powered by” relationships as more fully described herein. JobsLab.in does not share any personally identifiable information with third-parties, other than its partners as herein described, and will otherwise only share information in aggregate form. We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies from banner ads are collected by advertising networks, and we do not have access to this information.

 **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/settings/ads?hl=en). We also track users information using Google Analytics. Users can optout by [clicking here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). In addition, Google allows third party advertisers to serve ads on the Google Display Network. Using a tool created by the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), you can [opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) of several third party ad servers and networks cookies simultaneously.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

 **Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Employees are notified in staff meetings of security policies and practices regularly. Access to data limited and employees obtain access to log files by a secured password. JobsLab periodically reviews web security and ensures that all policies and practices are adhered to within the company. But since the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure, JobsLab assumes no liability for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized third parties.

 **Notification of Changes**  
JobsLab.in privacy practices may change periodically. JobsLab.in will notify users of changes only if the information collected from the user differs from that stated at the time of collection. JobsLab.in may also obtain the user’s consent by posting notice on the site.

 **Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
By using JobsLab.in, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, you may feel free to e-mail us with questions or concerns, but your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time.

 **How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact: JobsLab.in by Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
